Hubbell Trading Post records, 1882-1968 (bulk 1905-1950)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Sub-group V: Banking Matters, 1889-1966
  - Bank of America, El Centro, California, with Lorenzo Hubbell, Jr. January-September 1934 (Box 531, Folder 3)
  - The Bank of America, Flagstaff, with L.H., Jr., Oraibi. 1928-1929 (Box 531, Folder 4)
  - The Bank of America, Prescott, with Oraibi and Marble Canyon. 1938 (Box 531, Folder 5)
  - Bank of Commerce, Albuquerque: with C.N. Cotton, Gallup, JLH, Ganado. 1891-1892, 1903-1912 (Box 531, Folder 6-7)
  - First National Bank, Albuquerque: with JLH, Gallup. 1929 (Box 531, Folder 8)
  - First National Bank, Albuquerque: with JLH, Ganado. 1908, 1912-1917 (Box 531, Folder 9)
  - First National Bank, Albuquerque: with LH, Jr., Keams Canyon. 1913-1916 (Box 531, Folder 10)
  - First National Bank, Albuquerque: with LH, Jr., Oraibi. 1924-1933 (Box 531, Folder 11-12)
  - First National Bank, Farmington. 1930s (Box 531, Folder 13)
  - The First National Bank, Gallup: with Roman Hubbell, Ganado. 1925-1931 (Box 532, Folder 1)
  - The First National Bank, Holbrook: with Hubbell Parker, Ganaod. November 1934-January 1935 (Box 532, Folder 2)
  - The Gallup State Bank: with JLH and RH, Ganado. 1919-1924 (Box 532, Folder 3)
  - McKinley County Bank, Gallup: with JLH, Gallup and Ganado. 1912-1915 (Box 532, Folder 4)
  - Miners and Merchants Bank, Yuma: with C.I. Houck. November 1935-June 1937 (Box 532, Folder 5)
  - Union Bank & Trust Co., Los Angeles: with Hollywood Store. 1926-1928 (Box 532, Folder 6)
  - Union Bank & Trust Co., Phoenix: with Republican State Central Committee. 1911 (Box 532, Folder 7)
  - Union Bank & Trust Co., Winslow (The Bank of Winslow): with LH, Jr., Oraibi. 1924-1926 (Box 532, Folder 8)
  - Valley National Bank, Phoenix (The Valley Bank & Trust Co.): with JLH for Republican Finance Fund and LH, Jr., Oraibi. 1911-1914, 1934-1937 (Box 532, Folder 9)
  - The First National Bank, Winslow: with LH, Jr., Winslow and LH, Jr., Oraibi. 1929-1939 (Box 532, Folder 10-13)
  - The First National Bank, Winslow: check deposit statements (parts 1-2). December 1940-December 1942 (Box 533, Folder 1-2)
  - The First National Bank, Winslow: with LH, Jr., Oraibi. 1940-1942 (Box 533, Folder 3-5)
  - The First National Bank, Winslow: C.K. stub books. April 3-November 28, 1942 (Box 533, Folder 5a-5c)
  - The First National Bank, Winslow: C.K. stub books. November 28, 1942-May 8, 1943 (Box 533, Folder 6a-6b)
  - The First National Bank, Winslow: with RH. 1943-July 1946 (Box 533, Folder 6-9)
  - Valley National Bank, Winslow: with RH, Winslow. July-December 1946 (Box 533, Folder 10)
  - Valley National Bank: Winslow: with RH, Winslow. 1947-1951 (Box 534, Folder 1-5)
  - Valley National Bank: Winslow: check stub books. December 22, 1951-May 31, 1952 (Box 534, Folder 6-9)
  - The First National Bank: Winslow: WWII rationing accounts (coffee rationing). 1943 (Box 534, Folder 10)
  - The First National Bank: Winslow: WWII rationing accounts (gas rationing). 1943-1945 (Box 534, Folder 11)
  - The First National Bank, Winslow: WWII rationing accounts (meats, fats, etc. rationing). 1943-1945 (Box 535, Folder 1)
  - The First National Bank, Winslow: WWII rationing accounts ( processed food rationing). 1943-1945 (Box 535, Folder 2)
  - The First National Bank, Winslow: WWII rationing accounts (shoe rationing). 1943-1945 (Box 535, Folder 3)
  - The First National Bank, Winslow: WWII rationing accounts (sugar rationing). 1943-1945 (Box 535, Folder 4)
  - The Merchants Bank, Gallup: with JLH and F.M. Parker, Ganado. 1917-1919 (Box 536, Folder 1)
  - The Merchants Bank, Gallup: with JLH and RH, Ganado. 1926-1929 (Box 536, Folder 2)
  - The Merchants Bank, Gallup: with RH, Ganado and RH and Dorothy S. Hubbell, Gallup. 1938-1939 (Box 536, Folder 3)
  - The Merchants Bank, Gallup: with LH, Jr., Oraibi. 1934 (Box 536, Folder 4)
  - The Merchants Bank, Gallup: with JLH, Ganado and JLHTP. 1930-1931, 1944-1945 (Box 536, Folder 5)
  - The Merchants Bank, Gallup: with RH and DSH, Gallup, RH, Winslow, and Barbara H. Goodman, Winslow. 1940-1947 (Box 536, Folder 6)
  - The Merchants Bank, Gallup: with Winslow. 1943-1949 (Box 536, Folder 7)
  - The Merchants Bank, Gallup: with JLHTP. 1953-1959, 1962-1967 (Box 536, Folder 8-10)
  - Cancelled Checks. Note: Box 537 is stored in the vault. (Box 537)
    Includes the following:
    The Albuquerque National Bank, 1886, 1888-1890
    The Bank of Arizona, Flagstaff and Prescott, 1935-1938
    Bank of Commerce, Albuquerque, 1891-1892, 1902-1912
    The First National Bank, Albuquerque, 1923-1933
    The First National Bank, Gallup, 1925-1931
    The First National Bank, Winslow
    The Gallup State Bank, 1919
    McKinley County Bank, Gallup, 1919-1920
    The Merchants Bank, Gallup, 1963-1966
    Miners and Merchants Bank, Yuma, 1935-1937
    Union Bank & Trust Co., Los Angeles, 1927-1928
    Valley National Bank, Phoenix
    Valley National Bank, Winslow
  - Cancelled Checks: The First National Bank, Albuquerque. 1912-1917, 1927-1931Note: Box 538 is stored in the vault. (Box 538)
  - Cancelled Checks: The First National Bank, Winslow. 1925-March 1945Note: Box 539 is stored in the vault. (Box 539)
  - Cancelled Checks: The First National Bank, Winslow...becomes...Valley National Bank, Winslow. April 1945-February 1948Note: Box 540 is stored in the vault. (Box 540)
  - Cancelled Checks: Valley National Bank, Winslow. March 1948-July 1950Note: Box 541 is stored in the vault. (Box 541)
  - Cancelled Checks: Valley National Bank, Winslow. August 1950-June 1951 (Box 542)
  - Cancelled Checks: Valley National Bank, Winslow and Valley National Bank, Phoenix. July-October 1951, 1911-1950 (Box 543)
  - Cancelled Checks: The Merchant Bank, Gallup. 1917-1963Note: Box 544 is stored in the vault. (Box 544)
- Sub-group VI: Personal Materials, 1882-1968
  - John Lorenzo Hubbell: biographical, obituaries, memorial services; appointments, certificates of elections; Arizona State Senate; speeches; passport; invitations; automobiles: ownership, licenses; clippings, campaign posters, etc. (Box 545, Folder 1-2)
  - Lorenzo Hubbell, Jr.: personal, obituaries; appointments; medical records; white mule and foal; automobiles: ownership, licenses; miscellaneous. (Box 545, Folder 3)
  - John L. Hubbell: school work; dog registration; diaries. (Box 545, Folder 4)
  - Roman Hubbell: draft registration; clippings; automobiles: ownership, licenses; writings. (Box 545, Folder 5)
  - Forrest M. Parker: appointments; membership cards; tax receipts; inventory of property stored at Winslow; automobiles: ownership, licenses. (Box 545, Folder 6)
  - Hubbell Parker: bank book; school records; voter registration certificates; clippings; school work; miscellaneous. (Box 545, Folder 7)
  - Other Family Members: La Charles Eckel, Barbara H. Goodman, Alma Hubbell, Barbara H. Kuetter, Charles M. Hubbell, Dorothy S. Hubbell, Roman (Mony) D. Hubbell, Thomas S. Hubbell, Miles Parker, Adele H. Parker. (Box 545, Folder 8)
  - Employees and others: Harry C. Hibben, Howard C. Maus, Shine Smith, Thomas E. (Ed) Thacker, Thomas Tobin. (Box 545, Folder 9)
  - Ganado Gnat, vol.1, no.1. January 1927 (Box 545, Folder 10)
  - Academy Chimes, St. Joseph's Academy, Prescott. Spring 1930 (Box 545, Folder 11)
  - Drawings, plans, sketches, specifications for a variety of houses, lodges, stores, etc. (Box 545, Folder 12)
  - Samples of stationary, envelopes, checks, wrappings, forms, etc.; examples of catalogs, flyers, advertising cards, etc. (Box 545, Folder 13)
  - Addresses and calling cards. (Box 545, Folder 14)
  - Ganado Irrigation Project, Reservoir; notes. (Box 545, Folder 15)
  - Inventory of paintings, drawings, photos, etc. at Ganado. (Box 545, Folder 16)
  - Poems and verse in various hands. (Box 545, Folder 17)
  - Recipes. (Box 545, Folder 18)
  - Rugs and Indians: drawings and articles. (Box 545, Folder 19)
  - Voters lists; campaign cards (non-Hubbell); miscellaneous. (Box 545, Folder 20)
  - Personal Insurance: La Charles Eckel. (Box 546, Folder 1)
  - Personal Insurance: Dorothy S. Hubbell. (Box 546, Folder 2)
  - Personal Insurance: J.L. Hubbell. (Box 546, Folder 3)
  - Personal Insurance: Lorenzo Hubbell, Jr. (Box 546, Folder 4)
  - Personal Insurance: Roman Hubbell. (Box 546, Folder 5)
  - Personal Insurance: Forrest Parker. (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Personal Insurance: Hubbell Parker. (Box 546, Folder 7)
  - Insurance: American Central Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 8)
  - Insurance: The American Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 9)
  - Insurance: Calvert Fire Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 10)
  - Insurance: The Connecticut Fire Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 11)
  - Insurance: The Continental Insurance Co. (Box 546, Folder 12)
  - Insurance: Farmers Insurance Group. (Box 546, Folder 13)
  - Insurance: Fire Association of Philadelphia. (Box 546, Folder 14)
  - Insurance: Fireman's Fund Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 15)
  - Insurance: First National Insurance Agency. (Box 546, Folder 16)
  - Insurance: General Exchange Insurance Corporation. (Box 546, Folder 17)
  - Insurance: The General Indemnity Corporation. (Box 546, Folder 18)
  - Insurance: Gibralter Colorado Life Company. (Box 546, Folder 19)
  - Insurance: Gibralter Fire & Marine Insurance Company and the Home Indemnity Company, New York. (Box 546, Folder 20)
  - Insurance: Gibralter Life and Accident Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 21)
  - Insurance: Hartford Accident and Indemnity Company/Fire Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 22)
  - Insurance: The Home Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 23)
  - Insurance: Imperial Assurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 24)
  - Insurance: Insurance Company of North America. (Box 546, Folder 25)
  - Insurance: The Liverpool and London and Globe Insurance Company Limited. (Box 546, Folder 26)
  - Insurance: Lloyds America. (Box 546, Folder 27)
  - Insurance: Lumbermens Mutual Casualty Company. (Box 546, Folder 28)
  - Insurance: Maryland Casualty Company. (Box 546, Folder 29)
  - Insurance: The Metropolitan Casualty Insurance Co. of New York. (Box 546, Folder 30)
  - Insurance: National Reserve Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 31)
  - Insurance: National Union Fire Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 32)
  - Insurance: The Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 33)
  - Insurance: The Northwestern National Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 34)
  - Insurance: the Pennsylvania Fire Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 35)
  - Insurance: Saint Paul Fire and Marine Company/Mercury Indemnity Company. (Box 546, Folder 36)
  - Insurance: Springfield Fire & Marine Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 37)
  - Insurance: Universal Automobile Insurance Company. (Box 546, Folder 38)
  - Insurance: Westchester Fire Insurance Company of New York. (Box 546, Folder 39)
  - Newspaper clippings: political, local, Indians, marathon races, etc.: various newspapers (most not identified). (Box 546, Folder 40)
  - Materials relating to Forrest M. Parker's employment with Joannes Corporation (Coffee Products of America): employment, expenses, miscellaneous. (Box 547, Folder 1)
  - Materials relating to Forrest M. Parker's employment with Joannes Corporation (Coffee Products of America): orders and related materials. 1926-1927, 1929-1930 (Box 547, Folder 2-7)
  - House hearings and reports on postal cancelling machines: Hearings no.72 and no.73 December 1912, January 1913 (Box 547, Folder 8)
  - House hearings and reports on postal cancelling machines: Hearings no. 76 and no.78. January 1913, February 1913 (Box 547, Folder 9)
  - Memo books: diary entries and personal notes, notes on cattle and sheep, notes on mileages, lists of figures, etc.: Dorothy S. Hubbell. (Box 548, Folder 1)
  - Memo books: diary entries and personal notes, notes on cattle and sheep, notes on mileages, lists of figures, etc.: J.L. Hubbell. (Box 548, Folder 2)
  - Memo books: diary entries and personal notes, notes on cattle and sheep, notes on mileages, lists of figures, etc.: Lorenzo Hubbell, Jr. (Box 548, Folder 3-9)
  - Memo books: diary entries and personal notes, notes on cattle and sheep, notes on mileages, lists of figures, etc.: L.H., Jr. (Box 549, Folder 1)
  - Memo books: diary entries and personal notes, notes on cattle and sheep, notes on mileages, lists of figures, etc.: Roman Hubbell. (Box 549, Folder 2)
  - Memo books: diary entries and personal notes, notes on cattle and sheep, notes on mileages, lists of figures, etc.: others. (Box 549, Folder 3-5)
- Sub-group VII: Post Office Materials, 1885-1938
  - Audits of postal accounts. 1910-1935 (Box 550, Folder 1)
  - Transmittal letters: deposits of postal funds, remittances, surplus funds including money orders. 1912-1932 (Box 550, Folder 2)
  - Remittance letters, district office. 1932-1935 (Box 550, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous records. 1910-1938 (Box 550, Folder 4-5)
  - Money orders: remittance letters for surplus money order funds; certificates of deposit for money order accounts; statements. 1909-1922 (Box 550, Folder 6)
  - Star routes: arrivals and departures; route proposals, bonds, oaths; reports on performances of routes and notifications of deductions; route weight reports. 1908-1933 (Box 550, Folder 7-8)
  - Warnings and wanted posters. (Box 550, Folder 9)
  - Registered Mail: matter received and delivered. January 1, 1885-July 25, 1910 (Box 551, Folder 1)
  - Registered Mail: matter received and delivered. May 31,1915-March 24, 1925 (Box 551, Folder 2)
  - Registered Mail: dispatches. February 1, 1890-December 18, 1891 (Box 551, Folder 3)
  - Registered Mail: matter in transit. February 24, 1885-November 13, 1888 (Box 551, Folder 4)
  - Registered Mail: matter in transit. January 18, 1909-November 9, 1911 (Box 551, Folder 5-6)
  - Registered Mail: matter in transit. December 14,1912-May 12, 1925 (Box 551, Folder 7-11)
  - Registered Mail: matter in transit (part missing). September 2, 1925-June 29, 1931 (Box 551, Folder 12)
  - Window registration books. February 27, 1908-November 30, 1908 (Box 552, Folder 1)
  - Window registration books. January 19, 1909-February 22, 1912 (Box 552, Folder 2-5)
  - Window registration books. September 17, 1917-January 4,1922 (Box 552, Folder 6-7)
  - Window registration books. February 22, 1922-August 25, 1930 (Box 552, Folder 8)
  - Window registration books. August 26, 1930-October 10, 1932 (Box 552, Folder 9)
  - Insured mail: sender's receipts: October 7, 1925-January 25, 1927 (Box 552, Folder 10)
  - Insured mail: sender's receipts. December 9, 1929-September 27, 1932 (Box 552, Folder 11)
  - C.O.D.: received for delivery. August 18, 1925-January 10, 1934 (Box 552, Folder 12)
  - Special delivery, record of articles. September 24, 1928 (Box 552, Folder 13)
  - "Record of mail dispatches to Chin Lee from Ganado--Arizona." March 19-October 31, 1929 (Box 552, Folder 14)
  - Postmaster's account books. July 1, 1895-June 30, 1902 (Box 553, Folder 1-2)
  - Postmaster's account books. April 1, 1911-June 30, 1922 (Box 553, Folder 3-6)
  - Postmaster's account books. July 7, 1922-September 30, 1929 (Box 553, Folder 7)
  - Postmaster's account books. October 1, 1929-June 30, 1933 (Box 553, Folder 8)
  - Cashbooks. 1922-1925 (Box 553, Folder 9)
  - Cashbooks. July 1925-1929 (Box 553, Folder 10)
  - Cashbooks. August 1929-June 1933 (Box 553, Folder 11)
  - Money order register. January 1, 1913-December 8, 1930 (Box 554, Folder 1-5)
  - Money order register: Cornfields. April 21, 1931-March 15, 1934 (Box 554, Folder 6)
  - Money order cashbooks. January 29, 1909-June 30, 1922 (Box 555, Folder 1-4)
  - Register of advices received, money order; record of insured parcel post, sent and received. 1909-1929 (Box 555, Folder 5)
- Sub-group VIII: Sales Books, 1912-1963Note: All sales books are stored in the vault.
  - Big Mountain, Black Mountain, Farmington Farm, Ganado. 1912-1963 (Box 556)
  - Hub Store, Hubbell Service Station, Keams Canyon, Winslow. 1922-1953 (Box 557)
  - Ganado, Oraibi. 1938-1963 (Box 558)
  - Marble Canyon, Nakai Tso, Oraibi. 1918-1944 (Box 559)
  - Oraibi. 1938-1948 (Box 560)
  - Oraibi, Pinon. 1922-1951 (Box 561)
  - Pinon, Tenebito, Winslow. 1934-1952 (Box 562)
- Sub-group IX: Advertisements, Price Lists, and Catalogs
  This material, including many catalogs, has been arranged by type in mostly rather broad general categories.
  - Appliances. (Box 563, Folder 1-3)
  - Automobiles and parts. (Box 563, Folder 4)
  - Batteries, electrical equipment. (Box 563, Folder 5)
  - Candy, gum, nuts. (Box 563, Folder 6)
  - Chemicals, insecticides, paints, roofing compounds. (Box 563, Folder 7)
  - Clothing, furs. (Box 564, Folder 1-3)
  - Cosmetics, medicine and medical supplies. (Box 564, Folder 4)
  - Engines, motors, generators. (Box 564, Folder 5-6)
  - Farm, ranch, orchard implements/equipment. (Box 564, Folder 7-8)
  - Firearms, sports equipment, camping equipment. (Box 564, Folder 9)
  - Flour, grains, seeds, plants. (Box 565, Folder 1-2)
  - Furniture. (Box 565, Folder 3)
  - Groceries, meats, bakery goods. (Box 565, Folder 4)
  - Hardware, tools, gardening equipment. (Box 565, Folder 5)
  - Hats, gloves. (Box 565, Folder 6)
  - Hides, skins, furs, wool. (Box 565, Folder 7)
  - Horse-drawn vehicles. (Box 565, Folder 8)
  - Hotel/restaurant supplies/equipment. (Box 566, Folder 1)
  - Household goods. (Box 566, Folder 2)
  - Indian goods, imports, curios, novelties. (Box 566, Folder 3)
  - Jewelry. (Box 566, Folder 4)
  - Kitchenware, dishes. (Box 566, Folder 5)
  - Leather goods, luggage. (Box 566, Folder 6)
  - Linens, blankets, cloth, thread, yarn. (Box 566, Folder 7)
  - Musical instruments. (Box 566, Folder 8)
  - Notions, baby goods, gift items, watches, sun glasses. (Box 566, Folder 9)
  - Office equipment/machines. (Box 566, Folder 10)
  - Office supplies, paper goods. (Box 567, Folder 1)
  - Photographic equipment and supplies. (Box 567, Folder 2)
  - Produce, fruit. (Box 567, Folder 3)
  - Radios, phonographs, P.A. systems. (Box 567, Folder 4)
  - Saddlery and tack. (Box 567, Folder 5-6)
  - Service station equipment. (Box 567, Folder 7)
  - Sewing machines and accessories. (Box 567, Folder 8)
  - Shoes, boots, moccasins, slippers. (Box 568, Folder 1-5)
  - Soaps, cleansers, waxes, polishes. (Box 568, Folder 6)
  - Store fixtures and supplies. (Box 568, Folder 7)
  - Tents, awnings. (Box 568, Folder 8)
  - Tires. (Box 569, Folder 1)
  - Tobacco products. (Box 569, Folder 2)
  - Toys, amusements, fireworks. (Box 569, Folder 3)
  - Trucks and trailers. (Box 569, Folder 4)
  - Utensils/cutlery. (Box 569, Folder 5)
  - Belknap hardware and manufacturing co. (Box 569, Folder 6)
  - Berns wholesale sporting goods co. (Box 569, Folder 7)
  - The Breeden Corporation. (Box 569, Folder 8)
  - The Colorado Bedding Company. (Box 570, Folder 1)
  - Columbia Merchandise Co. (Box 570, Folder 2)
  - Continental Products, Inc. (Box 570, Folder 3)
  - The Country Store. (Box 570, Folder 4)
  - Deere (John) & Company. (Box 570, Folder 5)
  - The Denver Dry Goods Co. (Box 570, Folder 6)
  - Fairbanks, Morse & Co. (Box 570, Folder 7)
  - Charles Ilfeld Company. (Box 570, Folder 8)
  - Charles Ilfeld Company: replacement pages. (Box 570, Folder 9)
  - International Harvester Company. (Box 571, Folder 1)
  - The Isbell-Kent-Oakes Dry Goods Co. (Box 571, Folder 2)
  - Kendrick & Davis. (Box 571, Folder 3)
  - J. Korber and Company. (Box 571, Folder 4)
  - Momsen-Dunnegan-Ryan Company. (Box 571, Folder 5)
  - National Wholesale Company. (Box 571, Folder 6)
  - H.T. Poindexter & Sons Mds. Company. (Box 571, Folder 7)
  - Rice-Stix Dry Goods Company. (Box 571, Folder 8)
  - Richardson Dry Goods Company. (Box 571, Folder 9)
  - The Richter & Phillips Company. (Box 571, Folder 10)
  - The C.D. Smith Company. (Box 571, Folder 11)
  - G.A. Soden & Company. (Box 571, Folder 12)
  - Stockman-Farmer Supply Company. (Box 571, Folder 13)
  - Swartchild & Company. (Box 571, Folder 14)
  - Gallup Mercantile Company. (Volume 572)
  - Appliances-Trucks. (Volume 573)
  - Catalogs. (Volume 574)